Hey everyone, meet Kevin here. I just
finished another cup of coffee and I
could not be more excited to tell you
about how we just removed more
disclosure requirements for the AI
build-out so we can truly get this
bubble going to all-time new highs,
baby.
And a lot of folks have been wondering,
Kevin, why are you bullish for the third
and fourth quarter? You say you are more
bullish for the rest of 2026 than you
are for 2027.
What would leave you so mad? In fact,
we've got a price target on QQQ even for
upcoming Tuesday here in addition to
bullishness through the rest of the
year. But looks like we're about to hit
our price target for Tuesday early
again, which is all related to the
bullishness that's happening in the
economy. I'm going to break it down.
There are a few different things that
are going on and we're going to break
them down one by one. We'll talk CPI,
PPI. We'll talk about this disclosure
rule and what's going on with artificial
intelligence, Elon, all of it. So, let's
get started. First things first, if you
have not yet heard about it, you got to
know about this. So, if you hop on over
to the Meet Kevin app, you can use this
for free. I'm not trying to sell you.
I'm just providing more value, okay? You
have either desktop version, Android or
Apple, okay? You will find under the
data tab, under the artificial
intelligence section, a breakdown on the
removal of this
disclosure requirement. Now, this
disclosure requirement is a big deal.
Back in the financial crisis, we decided
that asset-backed securities, things
like mortgages or car loans that are
bundled together, should come with
certain rules. So, let's explain some of
those rules really quickly and use the
best eraser ever for a dry erase board.
You know what's great about it is it's
always with me.
>> [laughter]
>> Uh okay. So,
into after the 2008 financial crisis, we
passed these rules called the Dodd-Frank
Protection Act and other rules. And what
we decided in part was that asset-backed
securities, again like pools of
mortgages, should require the people who
actually make the pools to keep a 5%
uh unhedged,
okay? So, I'll put unhedged skin in the
game. So, in other words, you can't
create a product and then not own any
exposure to it yourself
because you might then not care about
the quality of the product. Whereas, if
you had skin in the game, maybe you'd
care a little bit.
>> [laughter]
>> Right?
Uh and the second thing is that we would
mandate disclosure rules uh for what is
inside. So, for the makeup, what
components are inside of these
asset-backed securities? Well, uh we
just uh did something
in the last
maybe 5 days here that basically said,
"Hey, if you're going to do an
asset-backed security on a data center,
well, guess what? You don't need to do
this and you don't need to do this.
>> [laughter]
>> We don't need that crap. Who needs
disclosure or rules? And that's
literally what happened here.
See, a group of attorneys wrote this
letter and said, "We respectfully
request that staff concur with our view
that fixed-income securities in data
centers, described as DCS, data center
securities
uh or securitizations,
uh do are not considered asset-backed
securities per the exchange act
definition, blah blah blah. This is just
a fancy way of saying, "Please exempt us
from the rules. The reason we think
we're different." And And this is kind
of like the the head-trippy math here
that they try to play is they say, "Hey,
when you hold a pool of houses or pool
of car loans, that is different than
holding a pool of GPUs.
You don't need to know what the
utilization rates are for those GPUs or
which GPUs are in the pool cuz it's it's
different this time. Houses and cars,
and this is their main argument, they
can sell individually cuz a homeowner or
car owner could decide to sell that, you
know, home or vehicle or whatever. But
GPUs don't sell themselves. And because
GPUs don't self-liquidate,
we're different and we shouldn't be
restricted by those rules."
>> [laughter]
>> Okay.
And so, guess what happened? Literally,
the day after they got rid of these
requirements that underlying assets have
to be disclosed, that ongoing reporting
requirements are met, that repurchase
obligations are disclosed, that GPU
rental rates, utilization rates,
concentration, lease expirations, and
all this crap is disclosed. What
happened the day after we said or the
SEC came out and said, "You know what?
In fact, we got a screenshot of it here
somewhere. I'll find it. You know what?
We agree with you. Here it is. There's
the letter. Based on the representations
in your letter, we agree that fixed
income or other securities issued in
data center securitizations of the type
described in your letter are not
asset-backed securities. In other words,
don't worry, the disclosure rules don't
apply to you because you're right.
You're different. Your pool is different
from 2008. And guess what happened right
after that?
Ta-da!
August 10th, Nvidia partners with
Apollo, BlackRock, Blackstone,
Brookfield, Goldman Sachs, and KKR,
basically everybody, to establish and
mobilize $500
billion worth of other
>> [laughter]
>> And they can hold the bag on GPUs
because these companies don't want to
hold the bag. All these companies right
here, they benefit from something known
as AUM, assets under management. They
really don't care what the assets are.
>> [laughter]
>> They just want their fee. And if that
requires now less disclosure, hey, let's
pop the let's let's blow the bubble up
even more. Is it a shocker that Nvidia
partnered? Of course not. They stand to
benefit probably 40% of that $500
billion goes straight into Nvidia's
coffers. So, reason to be bullish numero
uno before the big bubble pops and
everything comes crashing and burning
down into the worst great recession 2.0
ever, worse probably going all the way
back to the Great Depression.
Hopefully that doesn't demotivate you.
Between now and then, we've got
ourselves one heck of a reason to be
bullish cuz the spending is going to
continue. Man, I need more coffee. Not
only is the spending going to continue
because of these disclosure rules and
the Nvidia partnership and the
financialization of data centers, one,
but number two, we already know this, so
I'm not going to beat it like a dead
horse.
Elon Musk is going to spend like a
freaking drunk sailor. Elon Musk helped
SpaceX rally 9% yesterday because of the
day before that an interview was
released where Elon's like, "Yeah, I
just said our compute is going to be
like 99% of our company. Yeah, we're
we're going to spend 30 to 50 billion
dollars per gigawatt building these
facilities and and we're going to make
so much money. We're going to make 300
to 500 billion dollars a year in the
future." That's great.
Didn't mention the bottom line or GPU
rental rates or the sustainability of
those or how much debt SpaceX is going
to take on, but I'm not here to be
bearish on SpaceX. I'm telling you that
that is actually Reason number two to be
bullish is all the freaking spending
that is now
basically 2018 all over again on the
disclosure rule side.
Elon's spending like crazy
is all beneficial to the entire market.
In fact, I call it rising tide lifts all
ships, baby.
Some of the favorites that I have, uh
favorite number one in terms of index
level, RSP,
daily new highs over and over and over
again. This is the S&P 500 equal weight.
This is the third reason to be bullish.
As the equal weight rises, it means we
are rising beyond just what technology
stocks are doing. And what happens when
we see stocks go up beyond technology
stocks? We have a rising tide of people
getting richer, the wealth effect
expanding, and people will just continue
to spend every last freaking dollar they
have. Broad green market today, very
impressive, but it's been a trend. Look
at that equal weight. It has been up up
and away for frankly the last 6 years. I
mean, these these dips are very very
short-lived. And look how clean that
200-day moving average is. Now,
obviously, that's probably a you know,
symptom of being a moving average, but
boy oh boy, it makes you want to buy on
those 200-day moving average bounces or
buy at 200-day moving average bounces.
Now, the second portion that I'm also
very bullish on is IGV, the software
ETF. That's because of my Q3 Q4 software
bottoming thesis, which has really
started to play out with companies like
Microsoft and Palantir, and even Axon.
These are all great stocks that we've
sent buy sell alerts on. And I'm not
saying every single stock that I
invest in go straight up. In fact, I've
been in a place very recently where I
buy a stock and the next day it has
mornings and then it goes down and then
I'm like,
it happens.
>> [laughter]
>> You can't always win. Uh but if you want
the fundamental analysis, you always
know you can join over at meetkevin.com.
But let's focus. Let's focus on the
data. The next thing to make us bullish.
So number one, Nvidia disclosure rule.
Number two, Elon spending like crazy.
Numero three,
broadening the wealth effect. Numero
four,
inflation.
So this is an interesting one. Uh
inflation, which we're going to see
right here, you can see core goods had a
real tariff effect right here in a
balance and we've started to decay over
here on year-over-year core goods.
Core CPI is trending down. Core services
ex housing mostly flat over here and
housing has also been on a downtrend.
This has been the significant lagged
housing delay. This is actually what
Jerome Powell talked a lot about in 2021
and two that they thought housing
disinflation would come because of but
because of the way owner's equivalent
rent is calculated it would come with a
lag. That is actually exactly what
happened. You could see that lag very
clearly here how services reacted much
faster than housing.
Uh and now you are seeing some
flattening in that housing disinflation.
You're not getting as much anymore. Now,
who could have predicted this? Oh, wait,
we did. We literally made a prediction
that if Mondani wins, rents in Manhattan
will go to all-time new highs. And of
course, they have because anytime
a government tells you they are going to
make something more affordable, you can
put dollars and donuts on the fact that
they are going to make it more
unaffordable.
>> [laughter]
>> Government sucks.
Now, I'm not an anarchist, okay? Let's
be clear. There is some responsibility
that government has. There is a balance.
There's nuance to everything. Unfettered
capitalism just leads to pure socialism
and eventually communism. So, you need
some limits. I don't actually think it's
healthy what's going on with these SEC
disclosure rules. It is going to just
accelerate the bubble even more. And
this is why in the short term, bullish.
Longer term,
cautious.
>> [laughter]
>> Because it's a good way to put it,
right? But let's understand. So, CPI
came in a little lower than expected
yesterday. PPI was mostly flat this
morning. You can see the journal says
here, "Wholesale prices unchanged last
month as energy prices edged down."
Although that's not really true right
now with Brent at like $87.
Uh but uh so some of this is a little
bit lagging. But uh overall CPI and PPI
pictures were less bad than feared. Uh
the labor report softer. I will say
though, TS Lombard, who's basically been
chomping at the bit for a rate hike, uh
you know, even they are like, "Oh, uh I
guess this does uh lower the odds of a
rate hike in September. So, we're not
prepared to die on the hill of a rate
hike over here."
They've been begging for a rate hike.
And they that's sort of their base case
scenario at TS Lombard that this this is
this is it. This you know, this is going
to be a really big uh a big one.
Um but now the disinflationary numbers
that we're getting and the labor numbers
that we're getting or that are
deteriorating or actually indicating
there's probably no reason for the Fed
to hike. Instead, you can get Kevin
Warsh's anchoring bias to hold likely to
prevail. Now,
what's interesting is the only people
still calling for a rate hike like TS
Lombard are people who are literally
saying the following. We are more
overtly concerned about the labor market
rapidly tightening from close employ uh
to full employment to full employment.
So, in other words,
these folks literally think the labor
market is improving and that's going to
drive them to more
rate hikes.
I find this to be ludicrous. That's my
opinion. I think they're only looking at
the unemployment rate, which is going
down. But if you look at 27 weeks
unemployed, if you look at labor force
participation, if you look at the weekly
ADP trend, all of this data is bad. It's
a very muddy foundation, I call it. It's
not the straw that's going to break the
camel's back and push us into a
recession tomorrow, but it is a muddy
foundation. We are not on good
foundations with the labor market.
That's probably because more people are
going to lose jobs from AI before people
uh before we get more job growth from
AI. So, I want to be clear about that.
Long term, yeah, AI will create more
jobs just like any technology has ever
had before that. But there's usually a
delay, right? You lose more jobs first
and and then you get more growth in the
future.
Hopefully, that timing doesn't align, it
probably will, with the popping of a
bubble. But right now, we're still just
pumping air into this tire, okay? This
tire is rated for 70 PSI and we are just
at 50 or maybe we're at 69, I don't
know. But this puppy can stretch. We can
probably pump it up to 100, 120 before
it blows.
>> [laughter]
>> Maybe I'm too bullish here. But
I'm very optimistic and and that's one
of the reasons why I'm buying and you
know, why we're expanding our exposure
in a conservative way. If you want to
see exactly what we're buying and more
importantly why we're buying it, why
we're building the thesis that we are,
which is an enterprise inference compute
thesis, which has exposure to hardware
and software. If you want to see exactly
why and the fundamental analysis behind
all of this, always remember to join me
over at mekevin.com. Right now because
Elon is helping us pump it up, the
coupon code is called oh Elon, pump it.
God, Kevin, could you be a little less
caffeinated and more mature?
Oh.
Man, this is embarrassing.
Whatever. So, anyway,
um
when we put all of this together, we can
actually see there are a lot of reasons
to say, "Man, we're not going anywhere
anytime soon in terms of a rolling over
of CapEx." In fact, this uh
new $500 billion fund from Nvidia, I
think is completely underrated in the
market. Uh I don't think we've actually
seen the real hardware push yet. We did
see some of the push from Coreweave,
which then obviously led NVIS to move
up. NVIS Nebius.
NVIS is the ticker, right? Nebius is the
company.
Coreweave, which was really interesting,
had you know, a fantastic earnings
release, but it was really based on
their backlog, not based on their
balance sheet. If you look at
Coreweave's balance sheet, I'll pull it
up,
it makes me want to vomit. It is so bad.
And this is what I don't want to happen
to SpaceX is for them to get a crap
balance sheet. I want you to look at
this just so you can see it briefly
here.
They have $6 billion at Coreweave. And
if you look at their current debt that's
due within the next 12 months, and you
add it together everything in red here
not including the deferrals right here,
you have an $18 billion of bills due
within the next 12 months. And to pay
that $18 billion,
they have $6 billion.
There's no surprise here as to why
they're paying 10% or more in interest
on their debt. Now, what's actually
remarkable here on Coreweave is they
argue in their statement. Let me pull
this up because this is in the We have
this in our alpha membership as well.
It's under our stock tab.
If I go to Coreweave, I want you to see
their interest right now
expenses because they're kind of
misleading folks in my opinion.
This is their debt breakdown. And at the
bottom, you can see that as of June
30th, the company has a weighted average
cost of capital. So, um
you know, um
a WACC, a WACC, a WACC of 9%. Well,
that's great. They have a WACC of 9%.
But what's actually happening
is per the Wall Street Journal, they are
having to
raise uh the effective yield that
they're paying on this debt
by discounting their notes.
So, they're kind of lying to people.
They're able to tell you, "Yeah, our
WACC is just 9%."
Okay, but wait a second. Here's the Wall
Street Journal piece
that says the following.
Coreweave is the latest company having
to pay up a to attract investors in a
data center related debt sale. The AI
computing company just revised the terms
of its $2.6 billion leverage loan sale.
Mind you, a drop in the bucket compared
to the $18 billion they need to pay
their bills.
Offering yields of around 5.5 percentage
points above SOFR rates,
that debt would yield more than 10% at
current terms, which include offering
the loans at steeper than normal
discount values to par.
In English,
here's just ANOTHER WACC LIE.
>> [laughter]
>> THIS IS HOW YOU blow up a bubble.
Uh like I say, I'm not I'm not here
saying that, you know, the bubble's
going to pop anytime soon. It will pop.
Uh I don't know when, but it will pop.
But between now and then,
kind of bullish in the short term.
>> [laughter]
>> All right, ready for this? Let's say
you have a $100 worth of debt, and
you're going to tell everybody, "Hey, my
WACC is 9%."
>> [laughter]
>> It's less than 10%. What are you talking
about, Willis?
But what happens when you have to sell
this at a discount? They say, "Hey, um
uh these are $100 bonds. We'll pay you
$100 at some point in the future, right?
All a bond is is an IOU. So, we'll pay
you $100 back at some point in the
future. We'll also pay you a 9% yield,
so we'll pay you $9 for every $100 you
invest. But um we'll actually sell you
this bond for $85.
So, you're now getting a discount of
15%,
which if you're getting a discount of
15%, you're yielding nine dollars on 85.
You are yielding 10.59%.
So, on $85 due to the discount is 10.59%
Oops. Now you can still disclose to
everybody that your walk hawk is 9%
>> [laughter]
>> effectively
paying 10.6%
So like this is the kind of stuff I know
this is nuanced you know and if you like
it can
I just want a summary
so I say well then you miss all the
nuance and then you don't understand and
then so the people who actually watch
the videos which I think you do
obviously you're here
you know
your folks are like damn I never thought
about it that way I didn't know about
that disclosure rule damn I didn't know
about Corey's debt damn I didn't know
about how they can totally manipulate
the debt numbers like that
That is how we can all be more shady
together
>> [laughter]
>> Cuz they're all trying to screw us from
all different angles and so if you want
more of Kevin tearing apart a-holes like
an a-hole
join us at meetkevin.com bam it's time
for more coffee
>> Why not advertise these things that you
told us here I feel like nobody else
knows about this
>> Well we'll try a little advertising and
see how it goes
>> Congratulations man you have done so
much people love you people look up to
you
>> Kevin Paffrath financial [music] analyst
and YouTuber meet Kevin always great to
get your take